Anh Hoang Le

Contact

13751 Edwards Street, apt. 46D, Westminster, CA 92683 (951)-287-3584

anhhoangle1111@gmail.com https://github.com/rapityyy

Education

University of Califonia, Irvine

B.S., Computer Science, 2021 GPA: 3.5

Course highlights: Software design, project management & analysis, database administration, manipulating information systems & machine learning.

Skills

Python, C++, Java, HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Boostrap, Flutter/Dart, Github, MySQL, Linux, Microsoft Word & Excel.

Summary Of Qualification

Junior software developer, generating well-designed and efficient programming software.

Strong analytical skills, worked with technicians to troubleshoot complex system-level issues.

Strong background in management, programming abilities, and grasp of multiple technologies.

Highly organized, proactive, and obtain a team-oriented mindset and attention to detail. Amiable, diligent, and open-minded.

Projects

PocketChef | 2021

 A personalized app by user based on their weight, height & gender to provide them with recipes to cook for 3 meals a day. User is able to browse, adding and liking recipes.
 Generating a new menu everyday based on the user's preferences.

TicTacToe | 2020

Flutter app that works on both iOS and Android that utilize data structures & game logic.
 The app includes basic AI components for single player or 2-players local co-op mode.

Weather Machine Learning AI

 Competed in Kaggle competition using machine learning models such as classification, regression & neural networks to predict weather data points.

Professional Experience

Warehouse Supervisor

Hamle Supermarket | Fountain Valley, CA | April 2021 - Current

- Responsible for managing & training a team of workers. Analyzing issues in the warehouse to establish work procedures to meet demands & expedite production and workflow.
- Responsible for receiving & handling customer support. Maintain a good communication with departments of the business to allow faster and more reliable production.

Systems Administrator Intern

Groupo SMS Datacenter | Irvine, CA | September 2018 - June 2019

- Perform maintenance checkups and resolve issues for the client's data servers.
- Generating and handling clients support cases. Perform support and other technical tasks to clients through phone and operating using UNIX, private interfaces, & emails system.

Robotic Coach/Mentor

Gears2Robots | Temecula, CA | June 2014 - July 2016

- Responsible for managing/coaching a classroom of K-12 robotic teams students in local school districts. Classroom management while promoting a fun learning experience for students.
- Developing mechanical & software engineering courses to help train team members about building/programming a robot for FIRST Robotic competitions.